JOHN RUDOLPH M. LEE

Front-End Web Developer / Digital Designer

- B3 L2 Yakal St. Addas 4-B, Mambog 3, Bacoor, Cavite
- 09278542027
- johnrudolphlee@gmail.com

- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/john-rudolph-lee
- Bē https://www.behance.net/Dolphius
- https://dribbble.com/dolphius

My 7 years of experience as a Graphic Designer has afforded me a well-rounded skillset, including concept design, project management and communication abilities. I am also learning new skills like web development and just recently completed a coding bootcamp which enabled me to learn new technologies like: HTML, CSS, Javascript, MERN(MongoDB, Express.JS, React.JS, Node.JS)



Skills & Technologies

- HTML, CSS & JavaScript
- React.JS & Next.JS
- Node.JS & Express.JS

- Graphic Design
- Web Design
- Motion Graphics



Work History

2017-11 - Current Creative Digital Designer - Burst SMS

- Producing graphic illustrations that can be applied to web and print, ensuring high levels
 of productivity.
- Making animated GIFs for marketing ads.
- · Designing layouts, editing images and developing styles for websites.
- Contributing creative ideas during brainstorming sessions.

2017-01 - 2017-08 Freelance Graphic Designer - NomNom

- Producing graphic illustrations that can be applied to web and print, ensuring high levels of productivity.
- Designing layouts, editing images and developing styles for websites.

2015-06 - 2016-11 Web Designer - Tata Consultancy Services

• Handling day-to-day web design request using a site builder for US clients.

2014-01 - 2015-06 Web Designer - Hibu Philippines

Handling day-to-day web design request using a site builder for US clients.

2013-11 - 2014-03 Graphic Designer - Kethan IT Solutions

• Graphic Designer Internship.



Educational Background

2020-12 - 2021-04 Web Developer Career Program

• Zuitt Coding Bootcamp Philippines

2013-03 - 2011-06 Bachelor of Arts in Business - Industrial Management

• Technological University of the Philippines

2008-06 - 2011-03 Graphic Arts and Printing Technology

• Technological University of the Philippines